Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
What's wrong?
The mayor's never been
gone for this long before.
I hope he's all right.
It sounded like a battle
was going on in town.
There's been a lot more
cannon fire than usual today.
I'll go to town to check it out.
You all just stay here.
I'm going with you. No way.
There are still pirates in town.
It's too dangerous of a situation.
Yes, exactly.
That's why you'll need our help.
What kind of citizens
are we if we don't help?
We have got to find out what's happening.
You can't stop us from going.
We want to do all we can to help out.
Then it's settled.
We all go together.
In all my life, I've never
been as mad at someone as him.
That bastard Shank stole
countless riches from me.
I don't know how you two are connected,
but I can say whatever I want about him.
I've earned that!
The North Pole! South Pole!
That's what you say!
Right, and I'm gonna keep on
saying it because I'm right, clown!
Oh, you got guts?
I'm gonna settle this once and for all!
Go ahead and try!
All right, you bastard, I'm
gonna bust you up flashily!
Counterattack!
Knock it off!
Nobody but you two cares which is
colder, the North Pole or the South.
If you want to know so badly, then
why don't you go to both and find out?
Now call it.
The ship!
Enemy ship to the north-north-east!
Right. Get ready. Time to fight.
Yes, sir!
Yes.
I can't wait to plunder.
You seem happy, Buggy. Obviously.
Enemy ships are just like
big floating treasure chests.
It's only natural for
pirates to raid them.
Am I wrong?
Well, there's some truth to that.
You're too weak.
You and everyone else here
just don't have the pirate's
natural hunger and desire
for plundering treasure.
You don't know what it
means to be a pirate.
What's this?
It's...
huh?
Treasure map.
I've never seen one before.
It's incredible.
Is the treasure at the
bottom of the ocean?
Yes.
Now my life's path is flashily decided!
Hey, Buggy!
Aren't you gonna come celebrate with us?
We've found a whole lot
of really neat stuff!
It's no map!
I don't have anything hidden! Go away!
What are you talking about, Buggy?
Oh, uh, nothing.
You said you were gonna leave
this ship sometime, right?
So, what do you plan to do?
I'm gonna get my own ship, then gather
a reliable crew and see the world.
I'm gonna take my time.
Ha, all as a pirate, of course.
What a bunch of sentimental
nonsense! Say what?
I do admire your fighting skill, though.
If you weren't such a softy,
I'd make you one of my henchmen.
Your henchmen?
I don't think so. Huh?
We have completely
different outlooks on life,
so I think we should just
follow our own paths.
That's what pirates do.
You think you're such an expert on
pirates, but if we ever meet on the ocean,
then we'd have to have
a fight to the death.
Yeah, pirates do that too.
You never make sense.
Anyways, you said something about
finding some interesting loot, right?
Huh?
Oh yeah, we found a Devil Fruit.
A Devil Fruit?
I heard that the different fruits
are incarnations of the sea devil.
Supposedly, if you eat
one, you gain devil powers,
but the sea will hate you and
take your ability to swim.
You'd have to be stupid to eat that thing.
I'd never get that treasure on the
ocean floor if I couldn't swim.
But still, I bet you could sell that fruit
for at least a hundred million berries.
What?!
I, Pirate Apprentice Buggy, am
about to devour this Devil Fruit!
You gotta love the kids!
Never thinking of consequences!
Well, Buggy?
You feel any differently yet?
No, not really.
Aw, was it a fake?
I'm not surprised.
I've never seen a real Devil Fruit before.
Yes, that worked flashily well.
These guys are so gullible, I can't
believe I was able to trick them so easily.
Now to jump ship before
they find out the truth.
With the money I get from selling this
Devil Fruit and finding the sunken treasure,
I'll easily be able to form my own crew.
Hey there, Rocky.
Were you just saying something?
Oh, you!
Don't scare me like that!
Don't be so jumpy.
And don't steal too much
food from the kitchen.
You don't want to make the cook mad.
That was close.
Oh, yeah!
The captain told me to tell you.
Hey, what's wrong? Bastard! Why? Why? Why?
What's that piece of paper?
Not my map!
Hey buggy
What what's going on?
I can't move
Is it true that you lose
your ability to swim damn it?
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
What's going on?
Why aren't you swimming?
Buggy
I'll save you.
So, are you telling me
that Shank saved your life?
Yo, that's not the point
I'm trying to get across!
Because of what he did to me,
I was unable to swim and therefore
unable to obtain my sunken treasure!
Then I had a revelation.
If I couldn't go underwater, then I'd
just obtain all the treasure on dry land.
Using my brand new Chop Chop powers.
And now, I won't let anyone
who touches my treasure live.
Death to those who tried to build
for my hard-earned treasure!
Get back here, you thief!
Damn it!
He spotted me!
You don't stand a chance
of escaping from me! Now!
I'm going to flashily chop you off!
Ow, my balls, my balls,
that was a cheap shot.
Don't run off yet, we're not done.
Hey, you better drop that treasure
and get out of here, Nami.
You don't want him coming after you again.
No, drop the money and go?
No way, why should I
leave my treasure behind?
Did you just call it your treasure?
That's right, you heard me.
I'm a thief who steals from pirates,
and I just stole a lot of treasure
from a really annoying one.
So that makes this my
treasure now, understand?
Ah, that makes sense.
That's pure nonsense!
That's my treasure, and just because you
stole it from me doesn't make it yours,
you dirty, sneaky thief!
Honestly, what did your parents teach you?
A criminal trying to
lecture another criminal?
Ridiculous. What's that?
Whatever.
The day I take a morality lesson from
you is the day I stop being a thief.
I hope you're ready for the consequences.
Now, here comes Chop Chop Festival!
I'd like to see you try and save your
friend for me now, Gum-Gum! Damn it!
He broke up into smaller pieces!
What the...
Nami!
Give me back my treasure! No way!
See how you like this?
Dammit! Knock it off!
No, you knock it off!
Thanks for giving me
my treasure back, Nami.
Don't let go! You let go!
This is my treasure, so get
your grubby hands off him!
Just give me back my treasure!
Die!
I already told you!
You haven't finished dealing with me yet!
Consider that finishing move a
little gift from the old mayor guy.
Thanks a lot.
I owe you one.
Sure, no problem.
Oh yeah, the map!
This isn't over yet, Gum-Gum!
He's still alive! Shut up!
How dare you flashily do this to me!
You'll pay for this!
Assemble, Chop Chop Pods!
Huh?
Who looking for these, Buggy? Gah!
My box!
Ha ha ha ha!
All right! Here you go, B!
Stop it now!
See ya, Buggy!
Now come go!
Let's go go!
I win!
Whoa!
That kid sure's Captain Buggy flying!
So, what do we do
without the captain, huh?
Keep acting unconscious. Good idea.
Sorry your hat's all torn up.
Don't worry.
I can still put it on.
And I got Buggy out of here,
so I'm satisfied for now.
Bastard!
When I have time, I'll fix
it for you, if you like
What's that?
Oh, forget it.
I split this into two bags, so give
me a hand and carry half of it.
It's too heavy for me.
That sure is a lot.
If anything, that clown buggy knew
quality treasure when he saw it,
and now it's all mine.
I bet I can sell this for
at least 10 million berries.
Here you go. Huh?
It's the chart to the Grand Line.
You do want it, don't you?
You're giving it to me?
Because you saved my life.
Thanks, Nami!
Now I finally have it!
A map of the Grand Line! Hooray!
Oh, does this also mean you'll
be joining me and my pirate crew?
I told you, no matter what,
I'll never join a pirate crew!
But okay, hanging around with
you seems profitable enough.
Just remember this, I'm only joining
you because it's in my interest.
Sure.
Hey, Zoro, wake up.
Zoro, we're leaving.
Do we take care of everything?
Yeah, and we got a navigator, and
we got a chart of the Grand Line.
I'm not sure about this.
I feel lightheaded.
Of course you do.
It's always something
with you two, honestly.
Hey, wait a minute.
What did I do?
Are you kidding me?
You're the worst of them all!
Anyways, let's go help the mayor.
Oh, yeah.
I guess we should wake the old
guy up now that it's all over.
You there!
You're not residents of this
village? Nope. And who are you?
What was all that cannon fire we heard?
It sounded like there may have
been a battle here earlier.
If you know anything, please tell us.
Oh, good.
They're just citizens.
I thought that maybe
they were more pirates.
Oh, mayor! Oh, no! Say
something! Can you hear me?
He's out cold the pirates
definitely did this how horrible no,
I'm the one who kicked that old man's ass
Hold on you didn't have to tell
them that did you it's true.
Maybe you should explain to
them so they don't get angry
Tell me why exactly did you
knock our mayor out and leave him
in the street to die better
explain yourselves who are you?
Are you with the pirates?
They're getting really bloodthirsty.
We can't let them know that
we're thieves and pirates.
We're pirates.
Just as we thought.
It's the truth.
Pirates, how dare you ravage our town.
We won't show you any
mercy for what you've done.
What now?
Doesn't look like they're
up for a discussion.
Run!
How dare you hurt a beloved mayor!
How do you always make things worse?
This is a good town. Huh?
Everyone's so mad just
because of the old mayor guy.
Something tells me they're not gonna
listen to our side of the story.
We're turning here.
Huh?
Wait, hold on!
You gotta let me know sooner!
They ran into the alley!
Chouchou? Doggy?
Hey, move!
Chouchou, get out of here!
Those three are pirates!
They're barking at the wrong people!
Why isn't he letting us pass through?
Chouchou, get out of here! Woof! Woof!
Later, doggy!
That was close.
We only made it because of Chouchou.
Why do we have to put up with this?
Does it matter now?
We're done here anyway.
Yeah, maybe so, but...
Hey, is this your boat?
It's great!
It's nothing special,
but I guess it'll do.
I stole it from some dumb
pirates a few days back.
That's a big mouth you got.
We've been waiting for
you, you little thief.
Never thought you'd run into
us here, now did you, girly?
You know these guys?
Yeah, sort of.
Hey, it's not just sort of.
We're bound together by fate.
So these are your friends.
I guess we'll have to punish
the two of them as well.
It's time you learn what happens
when you steal other people's stuff.
Hey, you.
You hear me?
Take time for your medicine!
Hey, look!
He's waking up!
Thank goodness he's fine.
What happened here, Mayor?
What in the...
It was like this when we got here.
There were a few pirates when we
arrived, but they all ran off.
Can you tell us what happened?
Where are the young ones? What's that?
Are you talking about those three kids?
So they're still alive?
Those fools, treating a
senior citizen like that.
How rude.
We drove those pirates out of town, Mayor.
You don't have to worry
about them anymore.
But it's not enough.
We have to make them pay for
what they've done to our village
They deserve to be punished for
destroying the peaceful town.
We all worked so hard to build.
Yeah, she's right
There's still time to go after
them if we hold your mouth
I'm the only one who's allowed
to complain about those kids.
I won't let anyone else
badmouth them You hear me? What?
Why are you protecting
those pirates mayor?
Damn it?
They think they can just
disappear and that's that
Where did they go?
Well I think they were running toward the
port Damn kids they can't
just leave like that
I have a lot of things
I want to say to you all
All right let's get going can
I ask you something Isn't that
Buggy's mark on your sail well this
This did used to be Buggy's boat.
Think I should change it?
Hey, wait!
Young ones!
It's the old mayor guy.
I was ready to die.
I was ready to die filled with despair.
Thanks! Thank you!
Don't worry about it!
Take it easy!
Damn you, young ones.
I have no words.
What'd you do, Luffy?!
Don't tell me you left that
bag of treasure back there!
Yeah!
That bag was worth around five
million berries, you idiot!
That's right,
and they're gonna need
that money to repair
their destroyed town But
that was my treasure,
jerk!
Do you know how hard I worked to steal it?
Why didn't you do that?
No, I can't swim!
That's the whole idea!
If you want it, just go
back and get it then!
I can't do that!
You go get it! No!
That's dangerous!
I can die, you know!
I don't care!
And if you do that again, I really
will throw you in the ocean!
Well, for better or for worse, looks like
we finally have a navigator in our crew.
My way to that place.
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But if the world ever
changes, I call out your name.
We could return to the time
when everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream. You?